[Sniper] Move!
[muffled groans]
Luke.
[Sniper] I don't think so!
I want your cold wallet.
passcodes.
Then I'm gone.
I don't have a cold wallet.
Don't fuck with me!
[muffled speech]
[groans]
Tell me.
Or I start with your friend.
He's not my friend.
[groans]
And if I give you my cold wallet.
you're just gonna kill us anyway.
That's not gonna happen.
Really? 'Cause if I was in your situation.
I'd kill us both.
It's the only way you're getting out
of here clean.
- Have it your way.
- [Luke groans]
No. no. no. no. wait. wait. wait.
I have a. I've got a deal.
I've got a deal.
Oh! You've got a deal?
My cold wallet has five million on it.
But the other insider.
His has got 20 million.
Okay. I can take you to him.
And once you've got it. you let us go.
You're all right.
I'll take the five million here.
Look. five million is nothing.
it's nothing!
Just think about it.
Okay?
You're gonna have to leave
the country. right?
So. you. you're gonna need...
a new identity.
paperwork.
And that means forgers.
lawyers. accountants.
money launderers.
I mean. that's hundreds of thousands
gone right there.
And then you're gonna need
to live somewhere.
Pay people off.
Hush money.
Bribes.
What. what if...
what if someone spots you.
and you have to move country?
Or what if you get arrested?
Do you know how much it costs to fight
an extradition back to the UK?
Those cases go on for years.
Sure. if all goes to plan.
five million's enough.
But what if it doesn't?
But 20 million?
I mean. no one's extraditing you
at 20 million!
Gimme your cold wallet.
And we go get the other 20 mil.
Then I'll let you both live.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Passcodes.
And as part of the deal...
I get to take the gag off him.
Ah! Fu... Fu...
Fuck!
[reporter on TV] ...has done
nothing illegal. The resignation
comes in the wake
of the damaging revelations
that the Chancellor.
who's connected to a family trust
in the British Virgin Islands.
which has become embroiled
in the Lochmill Capital robbery.
Pressure had been mounting on
the Chancellor throughout the day
with the Shadow Chancellor...
- Shit's crazy.
- And the Opposition Leader...
calling for him to resign.
and for an investigation to be launched
into the Chancellor's financial affairs.
Well. despite the resignation.
the former Chancellor.
insists that there has been
no impropriety.
[phone ringing]
[Ellie] Rhys. what's up?
I'm locked out of my police account.
I'm trying to get into my case files.
Rhys. you're locked out of your account
because you're suspended.
Yeah. no shit. Ellie!
Yeah. and you're calling me up.
whilst suspended demanding witness files.
I can't give them.
What. are you serious?
[clears throat]
Is Fitch there with you?
No.
[telephone ringing]
Fuck!
[sighs]
Definitely not sacked them!
The man responsible for our tax system
being a giant tax dodger
had nothing to do with it.
- Move along. no story here.
- [phone vibrating]
So. what does the Prime Minister do now?
Rhys?
Have you been at the station today?
Not since this morning. why?
I need our files on Kate Shaw
and Milo Carter-Walsh.
Okay. but can't you just log-in to the...
Er. there's something's wrong
with my account.
Can you send them to me?
I don't have their files. Rhys.
They're on a ThinkPad at Lochmill.
Personal info stays on site.
The data protocols.
I'm not allowed to take any.
- Can you meet me there?
- Lochmill?
Yes!
Do you want me to come now?
Yes! Now. Darren!
Okay. I'll just get ready.
Okay. thanks.
Either of you try anything...
He's gonna kill us... and Milo.
as soon as he gets the cold wallets.
Oh. really? I hadn't noticed he was
a bloodthirsty lunatic.
Oh don't. don't.
Have you any idea what I've been through?
What you've...
You tricked me
into this whole fucking shitshow.
Milo told me everything.
You lied to me. And now we're all going
to end up dead.
I mean. I'm glad you're still alive. Luke.
but fuck you.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I got you involved.
I'm sorry about all of it.
but we're gonna figure something out.
- We?
- You. Zara.
You. you are gonna figure something out.
Like that bullshit you came up with
with Milo and the 20 million.
- I would never...
- Milo does have 20 million.
He didn't tell you. did he?
It's not nice when a mate lies to you.
is it. Luke?
- [car door opens]
- He's not in.
You're coming with me.
[reporter] Here with the news that tonight
yet more revelations
about the Lochmill heist are surfacing.
Whereas the previous leaks were just
in The Times.
these are on the front pages
of all tomorrow's papers.
Some of the Lochmill money that left
the Chancellor's account
has re-appeared in the tax haven accounts
- of three more famous faces.
- There's nothing on Morgan or Luke yet.
- A hundred million...
- That's good. right?
Sent to each of them. exposing...
Tomorrow morning if we're sitting
on that plane like we planned...
Then it's good.
We've got another job.
We need to leave now.
What about him?
Leave him here.
He's not gonna survive the night anyway.
[scoffs]
Come on.
[door creaks]
Holy shit!
[Sniper] Safe?
It's in the cupboard.
On the left.
What's the code?
Er...
Five-two-four-three-three-four.
[beeping]
Passcodes?
They're not here.
I mean. that's the whole point.
You're meant to keep them separate.
So. where are they?
A few places.
Only place you can get to tonight
is Lochmill.
So. we go to Lochmill!
You've got 20 million in your hand!
And no one's around this time of night.
We. we drive there.
walk in. get the codes.
Walk out.
20 million.
And it's a clean 20 million.
I siphoned it
through a bunch of exchanges. obscured it.
Your mates will never be able to use it
to find you.
Here. look. I've got the pass card
for the building.
It's 20 million quid.
[grunts]
Oh. my God.
Shit!
[mouthing] Oh. fuck.
[both gasps]
Oh. my God.
[groans]
[Zara] Oh. my God.
Right. Hey.
Leave him!
[Sniper grunts]
[sobs]
No passcodes.
no need for you two.
Wait. wait. I know. I know where
the passcodes are.
Erm...
We had a place
where we used to stash stuff
when we'd pick up.
You can get the codes and then
just lock us in there till morning.
You'll have a clean getaway.
Please.
Please. I'll. I'll take you.
Hi. this is Darren Yoshida.
Please leave a message.
and I'll get back to you
as soon as possible. Thanks.
[reporter] Now a week after the armed raid
at Lochmill Capital
and the fallout continues...
In yet more leaks released tonight.
a further three public figures
have seen Lochmill money
sent to their offshore tax haven accounts.
They are Russell Morris.
the owner of News Group.
the pop singer. Leonora.
and the TV comedian. Oliver Dav.
[phone rings]
[operator] Emergency.
Which service do you require?
[security guard] Excuse me.
Excuse me.
What are you do...
[neck snaps]
[gasps]
[Scots] What the fuck's happened?
Morgan got here first.
Looks like he's gone to Lochmill.
[London] Let's go.
I guess this is the part where
you lock us up and leave us.
No. it's not.
What?
We had a deal.
- [gun cocks]
- No. no. no. no. no!
[grunting]
[thuds]
[breathing heavily]
Zara!
Get. er... Get. get the gun!
Where's the key?
Okay.
What do we do?
Call the police.
It's dead.
The switch is in reception.
Yes.
Oh. for fuck's sake.
Hello. I'm Noel Johansson.
Here at Lochmill Capital.
we aim to provide
a better pension solution.
[touchscreen beeping]
[lift door opens]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
Luke?
Shit.
[Sniper groans]
Shit!
Where are the cold wallets?
Ah!
He's fucked you over again.
No. he hasn't. He's calling the police.
Course he is.
Have you used a weapon before?
What do you think?
Well. you're holding it wrong.
It's gonna recoil.
smash your fucking teeth out.
You're not gonna get me to look away.
Then just fucking shoot me then.
[screams]
[both grunting]
Hey!
[gasping]
[shuddering]
[Rhys] Police are on their way. Morgan!
You leave now. you can still get away.
Okay?
[shuddering breath]
Are you okay?
In there. come on.
[reporter on TV] ...the Chancellor
has agreed...
Where are you. you city boy prick?
[tyres screech]
[breathing heavily]
How did you know we'd be here?
I didn't come here to save you. Zara.
I came for Kate and Milo's files.
I thought I could solve the case
even if I was suspended.
It was Milo.
But he wasn't the one in charge.
He said there was someone above him.
that he never met.
And then. right before we came here.
we went to Milo's...
and he killed him.
Jesus.
[newsreader on TV]
and using tax havens.
Is this what the whole Lochmill thing
was about.
exposing tax cheats?
It's what links these people together.
Toby Gould. the Chancellor.
these latest revelations...
[reporter] Are you going to make
a statement. Oliver?
[commentator] It looks like they were
all hiding their money in tax havens.
I don't think anyone is surprised by this.
We've always known that the super-rich
hide their money offshore
to avoid paying any tax...
They never told you about all this.
did they?
[suspenseful music]
[Leonora on TV] I don't even know
what a tax haven is.
I can't get over it.
All I ever wanted to do
was just sing songs.
Music is my life.
Money is like. whatever!
[lift dings]
[Tall whispering] That's Morgan's knife.
Shouldn't the police have got here by now?
Yeah.
Shit!
We need to leave. Now!
What happened to hiding?
MI5. They must have intercepted my call.
The cops aren't coming. MI5 are.
We have to go. Now!
Fuck!
What now?
[Fitch] We wait.
Then we pick them up
as quietly as possible.
Make it look like nothing ever happened.
[Scots] Luke?
Luke?
Luke!
Where's Morgan?
Keep an eye on him.
Stay here.
[Scots choking]
No. no. no. don't! Don't!
Don't kill me. please.
- Please don't kill me!
- Shh. quiet.
Please. please.
What the fuck are you doing?
They'll see the light.
Just get ready to run.
[groans]
[grunts]
Oh. my God. Rhys.
- [gasps]
- [groans]
- Oh. fuck.
- I'm so sorry.
- Fuck.
Zara.
Where's Morgan?
Zara! Where's Morgan?
He ran after Luke!
Check he hasn't left the building.
[groans in pain]
I thought you said
there weren't gonna be any victims!
You said no one was gonna get hurt!
- None of this was part of the plan.
- There was a plan?
What was it?
Huh?
I mean what are you? Activists?
Terrorists? What?
[Rhys grunting]
Oh. you don't know. do you?
They never told you what the point was...
What the fuck does it matter?
- [gun fires]
- [groans]
[body thuds]
[breathing heavily]
Cold wallets.
Yeah.
[Luke grunts]
[lift door closing]
[lift dings]
Shit!
[London] Morgan?
You there?
Doesn't have to end this way.
You think we have any choice
in how this ends?
[gun cocks]
[gasps]
Come on!
[grunts]
You need to go and help your friends!
We need to move!
[Rhys groans in pain]
Come on.
Morgan.
[gun fires]
[thuds]
Yeah. police. erm...
Yeah. police...
It's fine. It's fine.
You sure?
No.
We need to stay in here.
He could still be in the building.
No. we don't know that.
You wanna go risk your life to check?
Or to get your money back?
What if he's dead?
What if they're all dead
and the money's just lying there?
MI5 will never let you leave here
with any of the money.
[groaning]
You're right.
We stay here.
[panting] Fuck.
[grunts]
[Rhys muttering]
No. fuck that!
This can't have all been for nothing.
Zara. Zara. Zara! [groans]
[unsettling music]
[sniffs]
[Zara panting softly]
[unsettling music rises]
[Zara breathes heavily]
[Zara screams]
[panting]
[Sniper sighs]
[breath shudders]
[Sniper] Zara?
Where are you. Zara?
We got your money.
[sing-song] Come get your money!
[clicks taser]
[Zara breathing softly]
Zara...
Come get it. office girl.
- [Zara grunts]
- [taser buzzes]
[Sniper groans]
[Sniper grunts]
[both grunt and groan]
[Sniper exclaims]
[both grunt]
[Zara grunts. pants]
I'm impressed.
You came back out here for your money.
[Zara panting]
It's not just about the money.
What was the point?
Why don't you go ask
your policeman friend?
Who do you think you are?
You fucking office girl.
[Zara grunts]
[Sniper groans]
[taser buzzing fades]
[Zara panting softly]
- [sirens blaring]
- [Zara groans]
- [sirens continue]
- [soft music]
[music continues]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[newsreader 1] So. these reports
are suggesting there was
some kind of disturbance
at the Lochmill Offices last night...
[newsreader 2]
hear a series of loud bangs.
Though when emergency services arrived.
they ascertained
there had been a gas leak...
[newsreader 3] The police
have confirmed that Lochmill employee
Milo Carter-Walsh.
who took his own life last week.
is now the main suspect in the robbery.
[newsreader 4] The Lochmill robbery
was two weeks ago.
and the revelations keep coming
as portions of the stolen pensions money
is routed through the tax haven accounts...
[newsreader 5] ...names have been dropping
for three weeks now.
Thirty-two celebrities with tax haven
accounts exposed so far.
[newsreader 6]
The world's biggest tax havens
are all British overseas territories.
British Virgin Islands.
British Cayman Islands...
[newsreader 7] ...even greater.
It's been a month
and it's still on every front page.
I don't think the government
can resist the pressure.
[news presenter] Well. there you have it.
The headlines from the Prime Minister's
hastily convened press conference.
The government will be
launching an enquiry
into Britain's overseas territories
and their role as leading
international tax havens.
The announcement comes
after days of pressure
with the fallout
from the Lochmill Capital...
[dramatic music]
- Morning.
- Hi.
[phone rings]
Hello?
[dramatic music continues]
[music stops]
[speaking indistinctly]
Erm. Warren.
from the Custodian Bank just called.
The four billion pounds...
The four billion that was stolen.
Yeah. You don't need
a description. Myrtle.
We know which four billion.
Erm. just. just like...
it's just been returned
to our bank accounts.
Like. just now.
[Coleen on TV] Milo Carter-Walsh.
What was he?
Financial terrorist. an activist.
or. or what?
Oh. I think the big question is.
I mean if it was him.
how'd he manage to move the money around
after he died?
[Janet on TV] Hang on a minute.
You can plan a financial
transaction in the future.
You don't actually need
to be alive when it happened.
- [Coleen] Wow.
- I mean. all that money he grew up with
makes you wonder why he needed
to steal a load more?
- [doorbell rings]
- [Judi] In all seriousness
maybe it shows that it doesn't matter
how much money you have.
- your upbringing is like...
- [Zara] Hello.
- [Luke] How're you doing?
- [Zara] I'm good.
Not be happy and maybe
this was his cry for help?
[Linda] It wasn't a cry for help though.
was it?
[Janet] Well. he did go on
and take his own life.
- [Linda] Did he. though?
- [Judi] I hear you. but I think it just...
[TV muted]
[Luke] We've been through this.
It wasn't our fault. Zara.
And Milo attacked that psycho
so he could keep his money.
You tried to stop him.
That psycho wouldn't have been there
if it wasn't for me.
We were just doing what we could
to save our lives.
And plus. Milo was the one that recruited
us into... whatever the fuck this all was.
That's the thing.
Don't you wanna know
what this was all about?
[Luke] We do know.
Someone wanted to fight the system. okay?
Reclaim the money. Eat the rich.
Whatever the fuck.
We just got caught up in it.
Wrong place. wrong time.
Do not fuck up the cover story. Zara!
Okay? We'll be back in the firing line.
We've done what MI5 asked for.
We've signed
their bullshit witness statements.
handed over our cold wallets.
We've blamed the whole thing on Milo.
In return. we get to live.
Look...
Let's get on that plane.
go sit on the beach.
drink a mojito. go get stoned.
And let's just. just move on
from this whole thing.
okay?
[softly] Yeah.
[Luke] Come here.
[suspenseful music]
[doorbell rings]
[Zara] Hey.
Hey.
You haven't been returning my calls?
No. I've just been really busy.
There's been a lot going on. you know.
Well... [sighs]
Listen.
I'm going away.
and I needed to ask you a question.
That night at Lochmill before Morgan...
died.
he said something.
I asked him what the point
of the heist was and he said.
"Why don't you ask your policeman friend?"
Are you serious?
I lost my job. Zara.
My debt got sold on
and the interest is through the roof.
I'm selling my house to pay it off.
When it goes through.
I'm gonna be homeless.
Plus. they nearly killed me.
How does any of that make you think
I was in charge
of a multi-billion pound heist. huh?
He's fucking with your head.
Zara...
Go through everything we did together.
On what planet would someone
who was involved do all that stuff?
[Zara sighs]
I'm being a dick. I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry about your job
and your house.
I don't want you feeling sorry for me.
Zara.
I'll sort myself out.
Kinda why I haven't been answering
your calls.
But I'm glad you came round.
Maybe when you come back. we could...
Yeah. sure.
- See you when you get back.
- Yeah.
[suspenseful music]
Hi.
Erm. I'm. I'm Zara Dunne.
I'm here to pick up some things.
Sofia said that they'd be here
for me to collect.
- [Donna] Yeah. she left them here.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
- [phone ringing]
- [indistinct chattering]
[Myrtle] Zara!
How are you?
I didn't think I'd see you again.
Oh. I came to pick up our stuff.
mine and Luke's.
To...
It's busy today.
Oh. you haven't heard. have you?
Well. the money's been returned.
Four billion. All of it.
Financial police have turned up.
Everybody is going nuts...
Wait. the police are here?
Well. it's...
really good to see you. Myrtle.
Thanks.
[suspenseful music]
[Zara] Rhys!
I know who it is.
Come with me.
[mysterious music]
[music fades]
Zara.
Rhys. What are you...
What are you doing here?
They've put you in a nicer office.
[sighs] Er. yeah. erm.
The four billion
got returned this morning.
That's why I'm here. er...
[Rhys] We know it was you. Darren.
I. I don't know what you're talking about.
The night of the shoot-out.
I asked you to meet me here.
You never showed.
But the thieves did.
How did they know we were gonna be here?
Then it chimed with something else.
How the thieves knew to be at Luke's
to abduct him before I got there.
How'd they know?
But you were with us with Luke
when we interviewed him that morning.
You saw him falling apart.
There's a pattern. no?
You get some info.
then the thieves turn up.
Two data points
don't make a pattern. Rhys.
[Rhys] Who does something like this?
They need to have money.
but hate money.
Know finance. but hate finance.
So maybe it's someone
from humble beginnings
who made a fortune managing investments.
Saw what a shitshow it was
and switched sides.
Now you're basing this one
on a personality type?
[Rhys] You're right. You're right.
So I called Nichols
to find out how you got the case.
I mean. it couldn't be the guy
who organised the heist
was the guy who got assigned to it.
Nichols cleared it up for me.
You're the Financial Crime Department's
specialist in this.
If something like this happens.
and you're available.
it's for certain you'll get the case.
But only if you're free.
In the week preceding the heist.
you turned down two new cases.
It's the only time you've ever done that.
- There. there was a reason...
- [laughs] That chat we had
about leaking the Gould-Simmons info.
That's why you wanted in
on the investigation. right?
If we're moving too slowly.
you could push us along.
Too fast. you could obstruct us.
You had to get the timings right.
Space out the revelations
for maximum effect
because this was all just
a giant PR stunt.
wasn't it?
All this chaos. For what?
A fireworks show.
Okay. you're right.
It was a fireworks show.
[Zara gasps]
[Darren] But it wasn't just that.
It changed the world.
Did you see the news today?
They've announced a government enquiry.
It'll take five years to complete.
then they'll ignore the findings.
Nothing will change.
- We'll see.
- People died.
I had to watch people die.
I didn't want that. okay?
It was meant to be victimless.
Why do you think I ordered Luke abducted.
not killed?
Why do you think I. I sent
the thieves here that night?
To. to neutralise Morgan. To protect you...
Bollocks! You just didn't want
the bodies piling up
because it would distract
from your... firework show!
I am not a monster. okay? I never wanted...
[Rhys] What you wanted doesn't matter.
What you did was dangerous and illegal.
And it was always going to go south.
For all your brains and training.
you're just naive.
It wasn't naivete. It's desperation.
It's everyone else out there who's naive.
interacting with the financial system...
- You sound like a teenager.
- Good! [slams fist]
Every time someone stood up
for something at personal cost.
- they were acting like teenagers.
- [Zara scoffs]
Adults who never lost their idealism.
who never gave in.
You called me a teenager to insult me?
I take it as a compliment.
Tell me why you shouldn't be in prison.
[Darren] This is...
Willemstad Bank and Trust.
I took a controlling stake
in it years ago. anonymously.
A tiny bank in a tiny tax haven.
This is basically the entire bank.
It's all in here.
That's how I moved the money
through all those accounts.
There's no cash. no gold.
not even any paper. really.
It's... It's just electrons
shooting around the world.
It's a construct.
An idea.
But who benefits?
Our system doesn't work for 99% of us.
yet we're. we're all forced
to pay into it.
Except for the ones at the very top.
The only ones who really
benefit from all of this
are the only ones
who can choose to opt out.
And tax havens is how they do it.
There's millions dying of hunger and
the people who decided this is how it is.
they're flying their private jets
over forest fires.
Why shouldn't I be in prison. Rhys?
Because I'm trying to stop
people being killed every day...
by an idea.
This isn't how you fix it.
[Darren] Now who's being naive?
Huh? [soft chuckle]
Everyone knows how nasty
our financial system really is.
How unfair. how damaging.
But no one does anything about it.
But you take something
like people's retirements.
Tie that to a story.
Suddenly people give a shit.
Suddenly. Prime Minister's on TV.
I returned the pensions to Lochmill.
But the money
from the tax haven accounts...
[Darren chuckles]
That's got ten million of Toby Gould's
slush fund money on it.
[Zara] You're trying to buy us off?
No. I'm trying to make a point.
[Darren chuckles]
Is it good money or bad
in that cold wallet?
Bad money.
And what if I give it to charity?
Is it good money. then?
Is it clean?
Or has it just polluted the charity?
Money's got a moral spark to it.
So what do we do?
Maybe we just...
try and do some good with it?
Maybe all that means is [inhales]
living a good life.
supporting good causes...
paying off our gambling debts.
Or maybe we use it to change the planet
so most of us aren't living in misery?
[whispers] Take the money.
And I'll know you're onside
and you'll never hear from me ever again.
All you have to do is let me go.
No. We. we take that money. Rhys.
We're implicated.
We are tied to him forever.
We just turned down 10 million quid.
We don't need his money.
I'm losing my house.
I could have paid off my debts.
Yeah. but you would have been in his debt.
This way we're free.
I'm not free. Zara.
What are you doing?
This is 20 million non-Lochmill pounds.
It's money Darren paid Milo.
Except there's no strings attached.
And you stood there the entire time
with that money.
just sitting on the table next to you?
No. I didn't know
if it would be in the box or not.
I wasn't the one who packed it. I was...
kinda just hoping. [laughs]
You risked 20 million quid
on kinda just hoping?
Well. it's like you said.
you're worried about losing.
you'll play badly and then you'll lose.
This is our winnings. Rhys.
[both laugh]
I can't believe you snuck that out.
But I mean. you said it yourself.
I was always going to get searched
after the shoot-out.
So I left my cold wallet
for the cops to find and stashed this one.
So what are you gonna do now?
I don't know.
Something exciting.
[rousing music]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today